https://www.harrissportsmail.com/usa/privacy-policy

sales@harrissportsmail.com
FREE US Delivery on Hardy items over $100!
Products on sale
Lures (101)
Line (23)
Accessories (22)
Hooks (21)
Rods (16)
Rigs (8)
Bait (7)
Reels (6)
Clothing (5)
Floats & Sinkers (5)
Luggage (4)
Bite Alarms (3)
Spools (1)
Brands on sale
Harris Sportsmail Privacy Policy
We are committed to protecting your privacy
Welcome to the Harris Sportsmail website. We appreciate your interest in us. When you visit and navigate our site and when you communicate with us via our site, we will not collect personal information about you unless you provide us that information voluntarily.
Any non-public personal information that you may provide via our sites will be used solely for the purpose stated on the page where it is collected. (In some cases, and in all cases where required by law or regulation, you will be able to update the information that you provide to us by sending us an e-mail) Harris Sportsmail will not sell, license, transmit or disclose this information outside of Harris Sportsmail and its affiliated companies unless (a) expressly authorized by you, (b) necessary to enable Harris Sportsmail contractors or agents to perform certain functions for us, or (c) required or permitted by law. In all cases, we will disclose the information consistent with applicable laws and regulations and we will require the recipient to protect the information and use it only for the purpose it was provided.
By "personal information," we mean data that is unique to an individual, such as a name, address, Social Security number, e-mail address, or telephone number. From time to time, we may request personal information from you at our sites in order to deliver requested materials to you, respond to your questions, or deliver a product or service.
Your E-Mail
We welcome your comments or questions about our websites and have provided e-mail boxes for that purpose. We will share your comments and questions with our customer service representatives and those employees most capable of addressing your questions and concerns.
Please note that your e-mail, like most, if not all, non-encrypted Internet e-mail communications, may be accessed and viewed by other Internet users, without your knowledge and permission, while in transit to us. For that reason, to protect your privacy, please do not use e-mail to communicate information to us that you consider confidential. If you wish, you may contact us instead via non-cellular telephone at the numbers provided at various locations on our website.
Other Information; "Cookies" and "Tags"
You should also be aware that when you visit our websites, we collect certain information that does not identify you personally, but provides us with "usage data," such as the number of visitors we receive or what pages are visited most often. This data helps us to analyse and improve the usefulness of the information we provide at these websites.
Like most commercial website owners, we may use what is known as "cookie" technology. A "cookie" is an element of data that a website can send to your browser when you link to that website. It is not a computer program and has no ability to read data residing on your computer or instruct it to perform any step or function. By assigning a unique data element to each visitor, the website is able to recognize repeat users, track usage patterns and better serve you when you return to that site. The cookie does not extract other personal information about you, such as your name or address.
We use a combination of both session and persistent cookies. Session cookies keep track of your current visit and how you navigate the site, persistent cookies enable our website to recognise you as a repeat visitor when you return. The session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will be removed on a pre-determined expiry date, or when deleted by you.
Most web browsers allow user privacy settings to block either all cookies, or third party cookies. Blocking cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one. Please visit www.aboutcookies.org for comprehensive information on how to change your cookie settings in a wide variety of different web browsers.
We may also use what is known as "client-side page tagging", which uses code on each page to write certain information about the page and the visitor to a log when a page is rendered by your web browser. This technique is also commonly used on commercial websites. "Tagging" does result in a JavaScript program running on your computer, but it is limited to providing information about the page that you are requesting and the configuration of your browser. It will not read any of your data files, or execute any additional programs. It does not extract any personal information about you, such as your name or address. You can prevent tagging by disabling JavaScript in your browser, but that may prevent you from using all of our website's functions.
You can view our cookie policy in more detail by following this link.
Information Collected
We may collect any or all of the information that you give us depending on the type of transaction you enter into, including your name, address, telephone number and email address, together with data about your use of the website. Other information that may be needed from time to time to process a request may also be collected as indicated on the website.
How do we use your personal information?
We may process your personal information for our legitimate business interests, e.g. fraud prevention/direct marketing/network and information systems security/data analytics/enhancing, modifying or improving our services/identifying usage trends/determining the effectiveness of promotional campaigns and advertising.
“Legitimate Interests” means the interests of our company in conducting and managing our business to enable us to give you the best service/products and the best and most secure experience.
For example, we have an interest in making sure our marketing is relevant for you, so we may process your information to send you marketing that is tailored to your interests.
When we process your personal information for our legitimate interests, we make sure to consider and balance any potential impact on you (both positive and negative), and your rights under data protection laws. Our legitimate business interests do not automatically override your interests - we will not use your Personal Data for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law).
If you have any concerns about the processing, you have the right to object to processing that is based on our legitimate interests. You have the right to object to this processing if you wish and if you wish to do so please email us at sales@harrissportsmail.com.
We use the information collected primarily to process the task for which you visited the website. Data collected in the UK is held in accordance with the Data Protection Act. All reasonable precautions are taken to prevent unauthorised access to this information. This safeguard may require you to provide additional forms of identity should you wish to obtain information about your account details.
Linking to Other Sites
From time to time, the Harris Sportsmail website may provide links to other websites, not owned or controlled by Harris Sportsmail, that we think might be useful or of interest to you. We cannot, however, be responsible for the privacy practices used by other website owners or the content or accuracy of those other websites. Links to various non-Harris Sportsmail websites do not constitute or imply endorsement by Harris Sportsmail of these websites, any products or services described on these sites, or of any other material contained in them.
Security
Harris Sportsmail has adopted and adheres to stringent security standards designed to protect non-public personal information at www.harrissportsmail.com against accidental or unauthorized access or disclosure. Among the safeguards that Harris Sportsmail has developed for this site are administrative, physical and technical barriers that together form a protective firewall around the information stored at this site. We periodically subject our site to simulated intrusion tests and have developed comprehensive disaster recovery plans.
Disclosing Information
We do not disclose any personal information obtained about you from this website to third parties except when we need to do so in order to complete the transaction. We may also use the information to keep in contact with you and inform you of developments associated with our business. You will be given the opportunity to remove yourself from any mailing list or similar device. If at any time in the future we should wish to disclose information collected on this website to any third party, it would only be with your knowledge and consent.
We may from time to time provide information of a general nature to third parties – for example, the number of individuals visiting our website or completing a registration form, but we will not use any information that could identify those individuals.
Changes to this Policy
Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our Policy. We will take reasonable steps to draw your attention to any changes in our Policy. However, to be on the safe side, we suggest that you read this document each time you use the website to ensure that it still meets with your approval.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you want to know what information we have collected about you, please email us at sales@harrissportsmail.com. You can also correct any factual errors in that information or require us to remove your details from any list under our control.
